https://www.larsondesigngroup.com/terms-of-use/

Retail Design
Septic Systems – Customized Design, Permitting & Landscape Solutions
Retail Design
Septic Systems – Customized Design, Permitting & Landscape Solutions
Contact
The following TERMS OF USE and PRIVACY POLICY are subject to change at any time at the sole discretion of Larson Design Group, Inc. Please visit the site regularly for updates. By using these sites after we post any changes to these terms, you agree to accept those changes, whether or not you have reviewed them or been notified about them. If at any time you choose not to accept these terms of use, please do not use this site or any of our sites.
TERMS OF USE
Please read the following terms relating to your use of this site carefully. By using this site, you agree to these terms.
OWNERS AND COLLECTORS OF INFORMATION
These terms apply to your use of all of the Sites and services owned, hosted, or operated by Larson Design Group, Inc. (collectively “we,” “us,” or “our”), including the following:
larsondesigngroup.com
bidplans.larsondesigngroup.com
ldgproposals.com
ldgretail.com
ldgtransportation.com
ldgbuildings.com
ldgfederal.com
ldgcivil.com
ldggeospatial.com
These terms of use also apply to any other site that we have owned or operated, do own and operate, or may own or operate in the future including social media sites (collectively, the “Sites”). Unless we say otherwise, all references to the Sites in these terms of use include all such Sites. These terms of use do not apply to your use of unaffiliated Sites to which any of the Sites may link or direct you.
If you have any questions about these terms of use you may contact us at:
Larson Design Group
1000 Commerce Park Drive, Suite 201
Williamsport, PA 17701
You may also email us.
RESTRICTIONS
The contents of our Sites are protected by copyright and trademark laws and are the property of their owners. All information on the Sites is copyrighted by Larson Design Group, Inc. Unless otherwise noted, you may access and use the information and materials within the Sites for your personal use. You may not change, modify, delete, display, transmit, adapt, exploit, or copy for distribution or sale any information, material, trademark, or copyright on the Sites. You must obtain written permission from us or any other entity who owns intellectual property on the Sites before you may publish, distribute, display, or commercially exploit any material from the Sites. By using the Sites, you agree to abide by all copyright notices or other posted restrictions.
LINKS
These terms of use apply only to our Sites, and not to the Sites of any other companies or organizations, including those we link to. We do not maintain, create, endorse, or take any responsibility for the contents, advertising, products or other materials made available through any other site, including those we link to. Under no circumstances will we be held responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any loss or damage that is caused or alleged to have been caused to you in connection with your use of any content, goods, or services available on any other site.
DISCLAIMERS
The information and materials on our Sites are provided “as is” and without warranties of any kind, either expressed or implied. We disclaim all warranties, expressed or implied, including but not limited to implied effectiveness of the ideas or strategies listed on this site.
Neither we nor any of our respective licensors or suppliers warrant that any functions contained in the Sites will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that the Sites or the server that makes them available are free of viruses or other harmful components. You (and not we or any of our respective licensors or suppliers) assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair, or correction to your system. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
Under no circumstances, including but not limited to negligence, will we or any of our licensors or suppliers be liable for any special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use, the materials or information on the Sites, even if advised of the possibility of such damages. Applicable law may not allow the limitation or exclusion of liability or incidental or consequential damages (including but not limited to lost data), so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you. In no event shall the total liability to you by us or any of our licensors or suppliers for all damages, losses, and causes of action (whether in contract, tort, or otherwise) exceed the amount paid by you to us, if any, for accessing the Sites.
PRIVACY POLICY
We are committed to protecting your privacy and security, and we use industry standard security measures to protect the information under our control, including firewalls and other security measures. Although the inherent dangers of the Internet mean we cannot guarantee the protection of your information against loss, misuse, or alteration, we work hard to protect all of your personal information.
We control this site from offices in the United States of America. We do not represent that materials on the site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Persons who choose to access this site from other locations do so on their own initiative, and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.
OUTSIDE SITES (THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES MAY BE DIFFERENT)
The Site contains links to other websites, and these sites may request information from you. In such instances, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. We do not control the privacy policies, contents, or links that appear on these sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third-party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.
HOW AND WHY WE COLLECT INFORMATION
As a visitor to our Sites, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as submitting an employment application or filling out the Contact form, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. None of the personal information you supply will be used for commercial purposes outside of our direct dealings with you, and we will not sell or otherwise distribute your email address or other personal information to any third party.
When you use our Sites, we or our authorized technology services provider may also collect certain technical and routing information from you to facilitate your use of the Site and its services. We use this information to administer the Site and to understand and measure traffic patterns on the Site so that we know which areas of our sites are favored by our users, which areas need improvement, and what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our Sites. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying you or any user individually. We may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.
This data is often tracked by us or technology services provider by using “cookies” during your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)
MISCELLANEOUS
These terms will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, without regard to any principles of conflicts of law. You agree that any action at law or in equity that arises out of or relates to these terms will be subject to mediation in the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. If any of these terms of use are found unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision will be considered severable from the remaining terms of use and will not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions. These terms may be modified only by our posting of changes to these terms of use on our Sites.
ArizonaNew YorkOhioPennsylvaniaWest Virginia
Get LDG News
Name
Email *
877-323-6603 | Email us
© 2020 Larson Design Group.
Corporate entities include LDG Land Surveying PC, LDG Engineers & Architects PC, Larson Architectural Group, Inc.    |    Terms Of Use & Privacy Policy
